Audiovisual Collection RRFA.02 RRFA.02.TEST2
RRF Test Repository
- Personal/Biographical, 1967 - 2008; 9.39 Cubic Feet; 247 Video Recordings 129 analog video recordings; 118 digital surrogates; 36 Motion Picture Films; 34 Sound Recordings
  - Television and serials
    - "Robert Rauschenberg: Inventive Genius." American Masters., Thomas, Karen
      - Raw footage, 1996-1997; 0.22 Cubic Feet; 22 Video Recordings 11 analog raw footage duplicates and window burns; 11 digital surrogates; 0.38 Cubic Feet; 4 Motion Picture Films interfiled camera reports and invoices original camera negatives; color Super 16 mm (Box 8, Object 7, Reg number 97.V017.00, Object 8, Reg number 97.V018.00, Object 10, Reg number 97.V019.00, Object 11, Reg number 97.V020.00, Object 12, Reg number 97.V021.00, Object 13, Reg number 97.V022.00, Object 14, Reg number 97.V023.00, Object 15, Reg number 98.V012.00, Object 16, Reg number 97.V029.00, Object 22, Reg number 97.V024.00, Object 23, Reg number 89.V004.00, Box 50, Object 1, Object 2, Object 3, Object 4)
    - "The Empire of Signs." American Visions, Episode 7. BBC., circa 1996; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings off-air broadcast recording (Box 8, Object 24)
    - "The Gilden Age." American Visions, Episode 4. BBC., circa 1996; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings off-air broadcast recording (Box 8, Object 25, Reg number 97.V032.00)
    - "The Shock of the New." BBC., circa 1980; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings duplicates of broadcast video recording (Box 8, Object 17, Object 18)
    - "The Walls Come Tumbling Down." Eye on Art. WNET., circa 1967; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 4 Video Recordings Film transfers; edited masters and outtakes; 0.27 Cubic Feet; 3 Motion Picture Films episode footage and outtakes; 1 color positive film with optical sound, 1 B&W negative film with optical sound and 1 color positive silent film 16 mm (Box 37, Object 11, Reg number 85.V046.00, Box 8, Object 14, Reg number 85.V114.00, Object 19, Reg number 85.V001.00, Box 45, Object 3, Reg number 75.MM003.02, Box 47, Object 7, Reg number 75.MM003.03, Box 48, Object 16, Reg number 75.MM003.01)
      Selects from "The Walls Come Tumbling Down" can be found in the "Mostly About Rauschenberg" file, in Series 7. Personal.
    - "Treffpunkt New York." Auslandsshow. ARD., 1983 January 18; 0.10 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings duplicates of broadcast master recording (Box 37, Object 26, Reg number 83.V001.00, Object 27)
    - Compilation
      - "Making More than One." An Art Series with Grace George Alexander." WNYE. and "The Print World of Tatyana Grosman," Part 2. Camera Three., 1976; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate; color and B&W; 00:47:40